RG 062:073, Town of Lisbon
Connecticut State Library
Town of Lisbon records
1877-1941
Connecticut State Library
Lisbon (Conn.)
7.5 cubic feet
Tax and election records for the town of Lisbon.
RG062_073
T000356
Historical Note
The town of Lisbon was incorporated in May 1786 and was taken from Norwich.
Scope and Content
Tax and election records for the town of Lisbon.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Lisbon; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Lisbon -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Lisbon -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Lisbon -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Lisbon -- Registers
Places:
Lisbon (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1877-1941
  - Rate books, 1889-1933 (Box Boxes 1-2)
  - Personal tax rate books, 1922-1934 (Box Box 3)
  - Old age assistance Tax rate books, 1935-1936 (Box Box 3)
  - Collectors' account book, 1890-1906 (Box Box 4)
  - Treasurers' account book, 1906-1913 (Box Box 4)
  - List of Voters, 1877-1908 (Box Box 4)
  - Individual tax lists
    - 1939 (Box Box 5)
    - 1940 (Box Box 6)
    - 1941 (Box Box 7)
  - Tax abstracts
    Tax abstracts for 1915 to 1932 are not boxed.
    - 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899, 1900 (Box Box 8)
    - 1901-1903, 1904-1906, 1907-1909, 1910-1912, 1913 (Box Box 9)
    - 1915, 1 volume
    - 1917, 1 volume
    - 1920, 1 volume
    - 1923, 1 volume
    - 1924, 1 volume
    - 1927, 1 volume
    - 1928, 1 volume
    - 1929, 1 volume
    - 1930, 1 volume
    - 1931, 1 volume
    - 1932, 1 volume